(Raj:)Oh, okay.
Uh, "Brothers and sisters
"I have none,
but this man's father
(Raj:)is my father's son.
Who am I looking at?"
(yells)
(Raj:)Yeah, yeah, we get it--
you want brains. Calm down.
(Amy:)Well, if I don't have a brother,
(Amy:)my father's son is me.
(Amy:)And if I'm this man's father,
then he's my son.
The answer's "son."
Ooh! There's a picture
of the sun over there.
(Leonard:)I bet the key's behind it.
Could be somewhere else!
Oh, got the key!
(Amy:)So, that's the key to the door?
(Sheldon:)That's it?
We spent $200
on six minutes of fun?
(Raj:)It's like when you bought that
remote-controlled helicopter,
(Raj:)and it just... flew away.
(Emily:)Sorry, guys. Really thought
the puzzles would be better.
(Amy:)Well, to be fair, we do all
have advanced degrees.
(Zombie:)Remember that
before you post on Yelp!
"If you were to die this evening
with no opportunity
"to communicate with anyone,